http://www.garagegames.com/company/privacy

Game Development Tools and Software
HomeProductsTorque 3DTorque 2DStoreHomeGenre KitsToolsArt PacksGamesCommunityWhat's NewBlogsResourcesForumsDev InterviewsMade with TorqueSupportDocumentationSubmit BugsPaid SupportServicesEducationCompanyAbout GarageGamesEmploymentLicensingLicensing FAQRSS FeedsLogo GuidelinesContact Us
Register
Login
Cart
GarageGames
Privacy Statement
Last
Updated: August 8, 2011
GarageGames.com
is an Internet service (the "Service") operated by GarageGames LLC. ("GarageGames," "we," or "us").
At
GarageGames, we respect the privacy of our users and the importance
of the information they entrust to us. We summarize below the basic
information policies and practices in place. To read the entire
Privacy Policy of GarageGames, please click here.
information"), such as your name and email address, (i) when you
(or other users) provide it to us when using the Service or in some
other manner, or (ii) from our affiliates, business partners, and
from other third parties. We may combine the personal information
that we receive from different sources.
We
also may collect other types of information in the following ways
when you access the Service:
Our
server logs automatically collect information, such as your IP
address, your browser type and language, and the date and time of
your visit, which helps us track users’ movements through the
games and other activities available through the Service and
understand trends.
We
may assign your computer one or more cookies which may collect
information to facilitate access to our Service and to personalize
your online experience.
We
may use standard Internet tools, such web beacons, which collect
information that tracks your use of our Service and enables us to
customize our services and advertisements.
We
do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the
age of 13. Should we ever become aware that we have collected such
information, we will comply with the Children’s Online Privacy
Protection Act ("COPPA").
Information
others may collect
Read More
We
may allow third-parties to display advertisements and/or collect
demographic research information through our Service.
We
do not provide any personal information to these companies.
These
companies may use tracking tools, such as cookies, to collect
information about computers used to view or interact with any
advertisements.
Some
of these companies may be members of the Network Advertising
Initiative, which offers consumers the ability to opt out of ad
targeting by all member companies.
If
you post information about yourself or others, or communicate with
others using our Service, please note that we cannot control who
reads your postings or what they do with the information you provide.
We encourage you to use caution in posting personal information.
How
we may use information we collect
Read More
We
may use information to:
Fulfill
your requests for products and services;
Customize
the advertising and content that you see on our website;
Facilitate
use of the Service;
Manage
your account and your preferences;
Analyze
use of and improve the Service, products, services and activities
offered through the Service;
Identify
and protect against fraudulent transactions and other misuses of
Service; and
Enforce
our Terms of Service.
With
whom we may share information we collect
Read More
We
will not share your personal information with others except as
indicated below, or except when we inform you in advance and give you
the opportunity to opt out. We may share personal information with:
Service
providers, such as credit-card payment processors, performing
services on our behalf;
Other
third parties in limited circumstances, such as complying with legal
requirements, preventing fraud, and protecting the safety of our
users.
We
may share aggregated, non-personal information in any of the above
situations and also with affiliates, business partners, advertisers,
demographic researchers and others.
Your
choices
Read More
You
may choose:
Not
to provide personal information, although that may result in your
inability to access the Service or use certain features of the
Service;
To
stop receiving promotional emails or newsletters from us by sending
an email, which includes your username and the email address linked
to your account, to legal@GarageGames.com;
To
review and update your personal information by contacting us at the
email address below or, if you have an account with the Service, by
logging into that account.
Security
Read More
We
take appropriate physical, electronic, and other security measures to
help safeguard personal information from unauthorized access,
alteration, or disclosure. However, we do not guaranty the safety of
your personal information.
Changes
to our Privacy Policy
Read More
We
may occasionally update our Privacy Policy to reflect changes in our
practices and services. If we make material changes in the way we
collect, use, or share your personal information, we will notify you
by posting notice of the changes through the Service.
How
to contact us
If you have any questions about this summary, or our information practices, please contact us by email or postal mail below:
Copyright © GarageGames.com 2000 - 2020 All Rights Reserved. Terms of Service - Privacy Policy
